const GeographyQuestions = [
    {
        question: "In which city is the Kaaba located?",
        options: ["Makkah (مكة)", "Madinah (المدينة)", "Cairo (القاهرة)", "Jerusalem (القدس)"],
        correct_option: "Makkah (مكة)"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the mountain where the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) received his first revelation?",
        options: ["Mount Hira (جبل حراء)", "Mount Sinai (جبل سيناء)", "Mount Everest (سلسله جبل اورينت)", "Mount Ararat (جبل الأرارات)"],
        correct_option: "Mount Hira (جبل حراء)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which river is often associated with the Garden of Eden?",
        options: ["Euphrates River (نهر الفرات)", "Nile River (نهر النيل)", "Tigris River (نهر دجلة)", "Jordan River (نهر الأردن)"],
        correct_option: "Euphrates River (نهر الفرات)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which continent is home to the largest Muslim population?",
        options: ["Asia (ایشیا)", "Africa (افریقا)", "Europe (یورپ)", "North America (شمالی امریکہ)"],
        correct_option: "Asia (ایشیا)"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the desert where the city of Medina is located?",
        options: ["Arabian Desert (صحرائے عرب)", "Sahara Desert (صحرائے صحراء)", "Gobi Desert (صحرائے گوبی)", "Kalahari Desert (صحرائے کالاہاری)"],
        correct_option: "Arabian Desert (صحرائے عرب)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which sea lies to the west of Saudi Arabia?",
        options: ["Red Sea (بحر الأحمر)", "Black Sea (بحر الأسود)", "Mediterranean Sea (بحر الأبيض المتوسط)", "Caspian Sea (بحر قزوین)"],
        correct_option: "Red Sea (بحر الأحمر)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which river is mentioned in the story of Prophet Musa (Moses) splitting it?",
        options: ["Jordan River (نهر الأردن)", "Nile River (نهر النيل)", "Tigris River (نهر دجلة)", "Euphrates River (نهر الفرات)"],
        correct_option: "Jordan River (نهر الأردن)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which city is considered the third holiest city in Islam?",
        options: ["Jerusalem (القدس)", "Madinah (المدينة)", "Makkah (مكة)", "Karachi (کراچی)"],
        correct_option: "Jerusalem (القدس)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which mountain range stretches across North Africa separating it from the Sahara Desert?",
        options: ["Atlas Mountains (جبال الأطلس)", "Rocky Mountains (جبال روکی)", "Himalayas (ہمالیہ)", "Andes Mountains (کوه اندز)"],
        correct_option: "Atlas Mountains (جبال الأطلس)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is known as the Land of the Two Holy Mosques?",
        options: ["Saudi Arabia (المملكة العربية السعودية)", "Turkey (ترکی)", "Pakistan (پاکستان)", "Iran (ایران)"],
        correct_option: "Saudi Arabia (المملکة العربیہ السعودیہ)"
    }
];

export default GeographyQuestions;
